Anthony Lewis Papers
Manuscript Division, Library of Congress
- Part II: Annual File, 1949-2007 (Box II:1-843)
  - 1988
    - "J" miscellaneous (Box II:416)
    - Kennedy, John F.
    - Kennedy, Robert F.
    - Kissinger, Henry
    - Kurds
    - "K" miscellaneous, (2 folders)
    - Latin America
      - Chile
      - El Salvador
      - General
      - Grenada
      - Guatemala
      - Honduras (Box II:417)
      - Nicaragua
        - General, (2 folders)
        - Linder, Benjamin, (2 folders)
      - Panama
    - Law
    - "L" miscellaneous, (3 folders)
    - Massachusetts Historical Society, Boston, Mass. (Box II:418)
    - Meese, Edwin
    - Middle East
      - Egypt
      - General, (5 folders)
      - Israel
        - Election
        - Press briefs
      - Palestine Liberation Organization, (4 folders) (Box II:419)
      - Strum, Philippa
      - Syria
      - Trip
        - General, (2 folders)
        - Notes
      - United States, (1 folder) (Box II:420)
      - West Bank
        - Al-Haq/Law in the Service of Man, (3 folders)
        - Awad, Mubarak
        - Beita
        - General, (2 folders); (6 folders) (Box II:421)
        - Releases, (2 folders)
    - Morgan, Elizabeth, (2 folders) (Box II:422)
    - "M" miscellaneous, (2 folders)
    - New York Times
      - Frankel, Max
      - General
      - Pulitzer Prize nomination
      - Staff, (3 folders)
      - Sulzberger, Arthur Ochs (Box II:423)
    - "N" miscellaneous
    - Obscenity
    - "O" miscellaneous
    - Paris, France, trip
    - Poland
    - Politics
      - Bush, George
        - General, (3 folders)
        - Mistress
        - "October surprise"
        - Platform (Box II:424)
        - Pledge of allegiance issue
      - Democratic National Convention
      - Dukakis, Michael
        - General, (3 folders)
        - "Smear"
      - Hart, Gary
      - Jackson, Jesse
      - Presidential campaign
        - General, (2 folders)
        - Meaning of (Box II:425)
      - Quayle, Dan, (2 folders)
    - Presidency
    - Press
      - Branzburg v. Hayes
      - Freedom of Information Act
      - Gannett v. DePasquale
      - General, (2 folders)
      - Great Britain (Box II:426)
        - General
        - Wright, Peter, (2 folders)
      - Libel
        - Annenberg Washington Program in Communications Policy Studies, libel project, (2 folders)
        - Boston Herald
        - General
        - Missing by Thomas C. Hauser
        - New Yorker
      - Murdoch, Rupert (Box II:427)
      - Singapore
      - Snepp v. United States and United States v. Marchetti
      - United States v. Morison, (3 folders)
    - "P" miscellaneous, (2 folders)
    - Race, (3 folders) (Box II:428)
    - Reagan, Ronald, (2 folders)
    - Rehnquist, William H.
    - Religion
    - Right (political conservatism)
    - "R" miscellaneous, (2 folders)
    - Safdie, Moshe, (2 folders) (Box II:429)
    - Soviet Union
      - General, (3 folders)
      - Rights, (2 folders)
      - Sakharov, Andrei
    - Speeches
      - Jan.
      - Feb.-May, (10 folders) (Box II:430)
      - June-Oct., (5 folders) (Box II:431)
      - Nov. 5-19, (3 folders)
      - Nov. 28, (2 folders); (1 folder) (Box II:432)
      - Dec.
    - Summit, United States and Soviet Union, Moscow, Russia
    - Supreme Court
    - Surroundings, (2 folders)
    - "S" miscellaneous, (3 folders)
    - Television (Box II:433)
    - Thornburgh, Dick
    - Tobacco
    - Turkey
    - "T" miscellaneous
    - Underhill, Marion
    - "U" miscellaneous
    - Vietnam
    - "V-W" miscellaneous, (2 folders)
    - "Y-Z" miscellaneous, (2 folders) (Box II:434)
  - 1989
    - Abortion
    - Afghanistan
    - Africa
      - Angola, (3 folders)
      - General
      - Mozambique
      - Namibia, (3 folders)
      - South Africa (Box II:435)
        - African National Congress
        - Disinvestment
        - General, (5 folders)
        - Human Rights in the Post-Apartheid South African Constitution, New York, N.Y., conference, (1 folder); (2 folders) (Box II:436)
        - Law, (2 folders)
        - Press
        - Sisulu, Zwelakhe
      - Zaire
      - Zambia
      - Zimbabwe, (3 folders)
  - 1989 (Box II:437)
    - African American Conference, Lusaka, Zambia
    - American Civil Liberties Union
    - Arts
    - "A" miscellaneous
    - Baker, James Addison
    - Blackmun, Harry A.
    - Book reviews, (2 folders)
    - Bork, Robert H.
    - Brennan, William J.
    - Bush, George
    - Bylines
      - Advertisement
      - General, (2 folders) (Box II:438)
    - "B" miscellaneous, (3 folders)
    - Cambodia, (2 folders)
    - Capital punishment
    - Celebrity Series of Boston, Inc., (2 folders) (Box II:439)
    - China, (4 folders)
    - Committee to Protect Journalists
    - Congress
    - Constitution
    - Courts, (5 folders) (Box II:440)
    - Czechoslovakia, (2 folders)
    - "C" miscellaneous, (1 folder); (2 folders) (Box II:441)
    - Defense
      - Biological and chemical weapons
      - General
      - Nuclear weapons, (2 folders)
    - Drugs, (3 folders)
    - "D" miscellaneous (Box II:442)
    - Economy
      - General
      - Savings and loan crisis
    - Education
    - Europe
    - "E" miscellaneous
    - Federal Bureau of Investigation
    - Frank, Barney
    - Free speech
      - General
      - Rushdie, Salman (Box II:443)
    - Fund for Free Expression
      - General
      - Randall, Margaret J., (4 folders)
    - "F" miscellaneous, (1 folder); (2 folders) (Box II:444)
    - Great Britain, (2 folders)
    - "G" miscellaneous, (2 folders)
    - Harvard Law School, Cambridge, Mass.
    - Harvard University, Cambridge, Mass.
    - Health (Box II:445)
    - Human rights
    - "H" miscellaneous
    - Immigration
      - General, (2 folders)
      - Mosala, Samuel Oxford, (1 folder) (Box II:446)
      - Suciu, Emil Ovidiu
    - Iran
    - "J" miscellaneous
    - Kennedy family (Box II:447)
    - Kissinger, Henry
    - "K" miscellaneous
    - Latin America
      - Argentina
      - Chile
      - Cuba
      - El Salvador
      - Grenada
      - Nicaragua
      - Venezuela
    - "L" miscellaneous, (2 folders)
    - Massachusetts Historical Society, Boston, Mass. (Box II:448)
    - Middle East
      - Amendment to the Prevention of Terrorism Ordinance
      - General, (3 folders)
      - Israel, press briefs
      - Lebanon
      - Palestine Liberation Organization
      - United States (Box II:449)
      - West Bank
        - Aruri, Taysir
        - Beit Sahour
        - General, (3 folders)
        - Isaac, Jad
        - Releases, (2 folders) (Box II:450)
    - Morgan, Elizabeth, (4 folders)
    - Morris, Errol
    - "M" miscellaneous (Box II:451)
    - New York Times
      - General
      - Staff, (2 folders)
    - Nieman Foundation
    - Nixon, Richard M.
    - "N-O" miscellaneous 2
    - Presidency
    - Press (Box II:452)
      - Branzburg v. Hayes
      - General, (2 folders)
      - Libel
        - Annenberg Washington Program in Communications Policy Studies, libel project
        - General, (2 folders)
        - Immuno AG v. Moor-Jankowski, (2 folders) (Box II:453)
        - Masson v. New Yorker Magazine, Inc.
      - Privacy
      - Singapore, (2 folders)
      - Snepp v. United States, (1 folder) (Box II:454)
    - Poland
    - Politics
    - "P Q" miscellaneous
    - Race, (2 folders)
    - Religion
    - Right (political conservatism)
    - Romania (Box II:455)
    - "R" miscellaneous, (3 folders)
    - Secrecy
    - Soviet Union, (2 folders) (Box II:456)
    - Speeches
      - Feb.-Mar., (3 folders)
      - Apr. 2-17, (2 folders)
      - Apr. 24-26 (Box II:457)
      - May-Nov., (7 folders)
    - Stone, I. F.
    - Supreme Court
      - Flag, (2 folders)
      - General (Box II:458)
    - Surroundings, (2 folders)
    - "S" miscellaneous, (2 folders)
    - Television, (1 folder) (Box II:459)
    - Terrorism
    - Thornburgh, Dick
    - Tobacco
    - Tower, John G.
    - "T-U" miscellaneous, (2 folders)
    - Vietnam
    - "V" miscellaneous
    - Wright, Jim
    - "W" miscellaneous, (1 folder); (2 folders) (Box II:460)
    - Yugoslavia
    - "Y-Z" miscellaneous
  - 1990
    - Abortion
    - Africa
      - Angola
      - General
      - Kenya
      - Mozambique
      - Namibia
      - South Africa (Box II:461)
        - African National Congress, (2 folders)
        - Disinvestment
        - General, (4 folders)
        - Law
        - Mandela, Nelson, (3 folders) (Box II:462)
        - Press
        - Revenge
        - Trip, (2 folders)
        - United States
      - Zaire
      - Zimbabwe
        - General
        - Zimbabwe Press Mirror, (2 folders) (Box II:463)
    - Arts
    - "A" miscellaneous
    - Berkman, Alan
    - Book reviews
    - Bork, Robert H.
    - Boston, Mass.
    - Brennan, William J.
    - Buchanan, Patrick J.
    - Bush, George
    - Bylines (Box II:464)
    - "B" miscellaneous, (2 folders)
    - California
    - Cambodia
    - Capital punishment, (3 folders)
    - Celebrity Series of Boston, Inc.
    - Central Intelligence Agency (Box II:465)
    - Children
    - China, (3 folders)
    - Cold War
    - Committee to Protect Journalists
    - Constitution (Box II:466)
    - Courts
    - Crime
    - Czechoslovakia
    - "C" miscellaneous
    - Defense
      - General
      - Nuclear weapons
    - Drugs
    - "D" miscellaneous
    - Economy (Box II:467)
      - General
      - Savings and loan crisis
    - "E" miscellaneous
    - Free speech
    - Fund for Free Expression
    - "F-G" miscellaneous, (2 folders)
    - Harvard Law School, Cambridge, Mass.
    - Harvard University, Cambridge, Mass.
    - "Hit list" to avenge the death of Meir Kahane
    - Housing
    - Human rights
    - "H" miscellaneous
    - Immigration, (2 folders) (Box II:468)
    - India
    - Indians
    - Indonesia
    - International Design Conference, Aspen, Colo.
    - Iran-Contra Affair, (2 folders) (Box II:469)
    - Iraq
      - Congress
      - Future, (3 folders)
      - General, (2 folders)
      - Past
      - President of the United States, (1 folder); (3 folders) (Box II:470)
    - "I-J" miscellaneous, (2 folders)
    - Kissinger, Henry
    - "K" miscellaneous, (2 folders)
    - Latin America
      - Cuba
      - El Salvador
      - Guatemala
      - Nicaragua (Box II:471)
      - Panama, (2 folders)
    - Law
    - "L" miscellaneous, (2 folders)
    - Massachusetts
    - Massachusetts Historical Society, Boston, Mass.
    - Middle East
      - Egypt
      - General, (2 folders); (3 folders) (Box II:472)
      - Israel, press briefs
      - Palestinian Liberation Organization
      - Syria, (2 folders)
      - United States
      - West Bank (Box II:473)
        - Al-Haq/Law in the Service of Man
        - General, (4 folders)
        - Khouri, Sam'an
        - Lawyers Committee for Human Rights
        - Releases, (2 folders); (1 folder) (Box II:474)
        - Sourani, Raji
    - "M" miscellaneous, (2 folders)
    - New York Times
      - Frankel, Max
      - General
      - Staff, (2 folders)
      - Sulzberger, Arthur Ochs
    - "N-O" miscellaneous, (2 folders)
    - Politics
      - Buchanan, Patrick J.
      - Clinton, Bill
      - Cuomo, Mario M.
      - Duke, David
      - General
    - Presidency, (2 folders) (Box II:475)
    - Press
      - Branzburg v. Hayes
      - Gannett v. DePasquale, (2 folders)
      - General
      - Great Britain
      - Libel
        - Annenberg Washington Program in Communications Policy Studies, libel project
        - General, (2 folders)
        - Immuno AG v. Moor-Jankowski, (3 folders) (Box II:476)
        - New Yorker
      - Pentagon Papers, (3 folders)
      - Privacy
      - Singapore
      - Snepp v. United States and United States v. Marchetti (Box II:477)
    - "P" miscellaneous
    - Quayle, Dan
    - Race, (2 folders)
    - Reagan, Ronald
    - Right (political conservatism)
    - "R" miscellaneous, (2 folders)
    - Silber, John
    - Souter, David H.
    - Soviet Union
      - General, (1 folder) (Box II:478)
      - Rights
    - Speeches, (2 folders)
    - Supreme Court
      - Flag
      - General, (2 folders)
    - Surroundings
    - "S" miscellaneous, (1 folder); (2 folders) (Box II:479)
    - Television
    - Thornburgh, Dick
    - Tibet, (2 folders)
    - "T" miscellaneous
    - United Nations, (2 folders); (1 folder) (Box II:480)
    - "U" miscellaneous
    - Vietnam
    - "V-Z" miscellaneous, (4 folders)
  - 1991
    - Abortion
    - Africa
      - General
      - Kenya
      - South Africa
        - African National Congress
        - Disinvestment
        - General, (2 folders) (Box II:481)
        - Law, (2 folders)
      - Zimbabwe Press Mirror
    - American Academy of Arts and Sciences, (1 folder) (Box II:482)
    - American Civil Liberties Union
    - "A" miscellaneous
    - Book reviews
    - Boston, Mass.
    - Brennan, William J., (2 folders)
    - Bush, George
    - Bylines, (2 folders)
    - "B" miscellaneous, (1 folder); (2 folders) (Box II:483)
    - California
    - Cambodia
    - Capital punishment, (3 folders)
    - Celebrity Series of Boston, Inc., (2 folders) (Box II:484)
    - Central Intelligence Agency
    - Chicago, Ill.
    - China, (2 folders)
    - Committee to Protect Journalists
    - Courts
    - Crime (Box II:485)
      - General, (2 folders)
      - Habeas corpus, (2 folders)
    - Czechoslovakia
    - "C" miscellaneous
    - Defense
      - Chemical and biological weapons
      - General
      - Nuclear weapons
    - "D" miscellaneous (Box II:486)
    - Economy
    - "E" miscellaneous, (2 folders)
    - Federal Bureau of Investigation
    - Free speech, (3 folders); (1 folder) (Box II:487)
    - Free Speech Yearbook, (2 folders)
    - Fund for Free Expression, (2 folders)
    - "F" miscellaneous
    - Great Britain, (1 folder) (Box II:488)
    - "G" miscellaneous
    - Harvard Law School, Cambridge, Mass.
    - Harvard University, Cambridge, Mass.
    - Health
    - Human rights
      - East Timor
      - General, (2 folders)
    - "H" miscellaneous, (2 folders)
    - Immigration (Box II:489)
    - Indians
    - Iran
    - Iraq
      - Aftermath of war
      - Civilians
      - Congress
      - Diplomacy
      - Future
      - General, (2 folders)
      - Great Britain (Box II:490)
      - Nuclear weapons
      - Peace
      - Press, (2 folders)
      - War
    - Ireland
    - Italy
    - "I-J" miscellaneous
    - Kennedy family
    - "K" miscellaneous, (1 folder); (2 folders) (Box II:491)
    - Latin America
      - El Salvador
      - General
      - Nicaragua
    - Law
    - "L" miscellaneous, (2 folders)
    - Marshall, Thurgood
    - Martin, Dannie M., (4 folders) (Box II:492)
    - Massachusetts
    - Massachusetts Historical Society, Boston, Mass.
    - Middle East
      - Egypt, (2 folders)
      - General, (3 folders) (Box II:493)
      - Palestine Liberation Organization
      - Syria
      - Trip
      - United States
      - West Bank
        - General, (1 folder) (Box II:494)
        - Jabarin, Shawan, (2 folders)
        - Nusseibeh, Sari
        - Releases, (2 folders)
        - Shriteh, Taher
    - "M" miscellaneous
    - New York Times
      - Fellowship
      - General
      - Staff, (2 folders) (Box II:495)
    - Nixon, Richard M.
    - "N-O" miscellaneous, (2 folders)
    - Politics, (2 folders)
    - Presidency
    - Press
      - Branzburg v. Hayes
      - Freedom of Information Act (Box II:496)
      - General
      - Great Britain
      - Libel
        - General, (3 folders)
        - Immuno AG v. Moor-Jankowski, (2 folders); (1 folder) (Box II:497)
        - Masson v. New Yorker Magazine, Inc.
      - Maxwell, Robert
    - "P-Q" miscellaneous
    - Race, (2 folders); (4 folders) (Box II:498)
    - "R" miscellaneous, (2 folders)
    - Soviet Union
      - Crisis, (1 folder); (2 folders) (Box II:499)
      - General, (3 folders)
    - Speeches
      - Feb., (1 folder); (2 folders) (Box II:500)
      - Mar.-May, (6 folders)
      - June-Aug., (5 folders) (Box II:501)
      - Sept. 4, (2 folders); (1 folder) (Box II:502)
      - Sept 9-28, (4 folders)
      - Oct. 1-17, (2 folders)
      - Oct. 21-23, (1 folder) (Box II:503)
      - Oct. 28-31
      - Nov.-Dec., (6 folders)
    - Supreme Court, (7 folders) (Box II:504)
    - Surroundings, (2 folders) (Box II:505)
    - "S" miscellaneous, (3 folders)
    - Television, (1 folder); (2 folders) (Box II:506)
    - Terrorism
    - Thomas, Clarence, (4 folders)
    - Turkey (Box II:507)
    - "T-U" miscellaneous
    - Vietnam
    - "V-W" miscellaneous, (3 folders)
    - Yugoslavia
    - "Y-Z" miscellaneous
  - 1992 (Box II:508)
    - Abortion, (2 folders)
    - Africa
      - Angola
      - General
      - Mozambique
      - Somalia
      - South Africa
        - General, (2 folders)
        - Law
        - Nieman Foundation, African-American Institute, South and Southern Africa Media Conference
        - Transkei
        - Trip, (2 folders) (Box II:509)
      - Zaire
      - Zimbabwe
        - Drought
        - General, (2 folders)
        - Trip
        - Zimbabwe Press Mirror, (2 folders)
    - African-American Institute, New York, N.Y.
    - AIDS (disease)
    - American Academy of Arts and Sciences, (1 folder) (Box II:510)
    - Arts
    - Australia
    - "A" miscellaneous, (2 folders)
    - Barr, William Pelham, (2 folders)
    - Book reviews, (2 folders)
    - Bork, Robert H.
    - Boston, Mass. (Box II:511)
    - Brennan, William J., oral history
    - Burma, (2 folders)
    - Bush, George
      - Campaign "tricks"
      - General, (4 folders)
      - Iran-Contra Affair, (3 folders)
      - Vetoes (Box II:512)
    - Bylines
    - "B" miscellaneous, (5 folders)
    - California
    - Capital punishment, (1 folder) (Box II:513)
    - Celebrity Series of Boston, Inc.
    - Censorship
    - Central Intelligence Agency
    - China, (2 folders)
    - Clinton, Bill, transition, (3 folders)
    - Committee to Protect Journalists, (1 folder); (3 folders) (Box II:514)
    - Congress
    - Constitution
    - Courts
      - Carnes, Edward E., (3 folders)
      - General
    - Crime
    - "C" miscellaneous, (1 folder) (Box II:515)
    - Defense
    - Democratic National Convention
    - Drugs
    - "D" miscellaneous
    - Economy
      - General, (4 folders); (1 folder) (Box II:516)
      - Savings and loan crisis
    - Education, (2 folders)
    - Europe
    - "E" miscellaneous
    - Free speech, (3 folders); (1 folder) (Box II:517)
    - Freund, Paul A., (4 folders)
    - Fund for Free Expression, (2 folders)
    - "F" miscellaneous, (2 folders)
    - Gideon's Trumpet, (3 folders) (Box II:518)
    - Great Britain
      - General, (3 folders)
      - Trip
    - "G" miscellaneous, (1 folder) (Box II:519)
    - Haiti, (5 folders); (2 folders) (Box II:520)
    - Harvard Law School, Cambridge, Mass.
    - Harvard Magazine
    - Harvard University, Cambridge, Mass.
    - Health
    - Human rights
      - East Timor
      - General, (2 folders)
    - "H" miscellaneous, (2 folders)
    - Immigration, (2 folders) (Box II:521)
    - Iran
    - Iraq
      - Civilians
      - General, (2 folders)
    - Ireland
    - "I" miscellaneous
    - Japan
    - JFK (motion picture)
    - "J" miscellaneous
    - Kennedy family
    - Kissinger, Henry (Box II:522)
    - "K" miscellaneous, (2 folders)
    - Latin America
      - Cuba
      - El Salvador
      - General
      - Nicaragua
      - Panama
    - "L" miscellaneous, (3 folders)
    - Massachusetts
    - Massachusetts Historical Society, Boston, Mass., (2 folders)
    - Middle East
      - Egypt
        - General
        - Peace conference, (2 folders) (Box II:523)
        - Rights, (2 folders)
        - Trip
      - General, (3 folders)
      - Israel, trip, (3 folders)
      - Kuwait (Box II:524)
      - Libya
      - Palestine Liberation Organization
      - Syria
      - Trip
      - United States, (2 folders)
      - Vanunu, Mordechai
      - West Bank
        - General, (2 folders)
        - Releases
        - Shikaki, Khalil
    - "M" miscellaneous, (1 folder); (2 folders) (Box II:525)
    - New York Times
      - Fellowship
      - Frankel, Max
      - General
      - Pulitzer Prize, Linda Greenhouse
      - Staff, (2 folders)
      - Sulzberger, Arthur Ochs
    - Nieman Foundation
    - Nixon, Richard M. (Box II:526)
    - "N" miscellaneous
    - Obscenity
    - "O" miscellaneous
    - Politics
      - Brown, Jerry
      - Clinton, Bill, (2 folders)
      - Cuomo, Mario M.
      - General, (2 folders) (Box II:527)
      - Perot, H. Ross, (3 folders)
      - Presidency
      - Presidential debate
    - Press
      - Branzburg v. Hayes, (1 folder) (Box II:528)
      - General, (2 folders)
      - Great Britain, (2 folders)
      - Libel
        - Bachchan v. India Abroad Publications, (1 folder); (3 folders) (Box II:529)
        - First Amendment Law Letter
        - General
        - Halcion
        - Immuno AG v. Moor-Jankowski
        - Masson v. New Yorker Magazine, Inc.
      - Privacy
    - "P" miscellaneous, (2 folders) (Box II:530)
    - Quayle, Dan
    - "Q" miscellaneous
    - Race
      - General, (2 folders)
      - Los Angeles, Calif.
    - Religion
    - Republican National Convention
    - Right (political and religious conservatism), (1 folder) (Box II:531)
    - Russia
    - "R" miscellaneous, (3 folders)
    - Secrecy
    - Speeches
      - Jan.-Mar.
      - Mar., (2 folders) (Box II:532)
      - Apr., (3 folders)
      - May, (2 folders) (Box II:533)
      - June, (5 folders)
      - Aug., (1 folder) (Box II:534)
      - Sept.-Oct., (6 folders)
      - Nov.-Dec., (5 folders) (Box II:535)
    - Supreme Court, (2 folders); (1 folder) (Box II:536)
    - Surroundings, (2 folders)
    - "S" miscellaneous, (3 folders); (1 folder) (Box II:537)
    - Televison
    - Tobacco
    - Turkey
    - "T-U" miscellaneous, (2 folders)
    - Vietnam
    - "V-W" miscellaneous, (5 folders)
    - Yugoslavia, (8 folders); (3 folders) (Box II:538, Box II:539)
    - "Y-Z" miscellaneous, (2 folders)
  - 1993
    - Abortion, (3 folders)
    - Africa
      - Angola
      - Ethiopia
      - General
      - Namibia
      - Somalia
      - South Africa (Box II:540)
        - African National Congress
        - Disinvestment
        - General, (2 folders)
        - Law, (2 folders)
        - Negotiations, (3 folders)
        - Trip, (2 folders) (Box II:541)
        - United States
      - Sudan
      - Transkei
      - Zaire
      - Zimbabwe
        - General
        - Trip
        - Zimbabwe Press Mirror, (2 folders)
    - American Academy of Arts and Sciences, (3 folders) (Box II:542)
    - Armenia
    - Asia
      - Cambodia
        - General
        - Trip, (2 folders)
      - General
      - Hong Kong
        - General
        - Trip (Box II:543)
      - India
      - Singapore
        - General
        - Trip, (2 folders)
      - Thailand
        - General
        - Trip, (2 folders)
      - Trip, (2 folders)
    - Arts, (3 folders) (Box II:544)
    - Australia
    - "A" miscellaneous, (2 folders)
    - Baird, Zoë E., (2 folders)
    - Book reviews, (2 folders); (1 folder) (Box II:545)
    - Breyer, Stephen G.
    - Burma
    - Bush, George
    - Bylines, (2 folders)
    - "B" miscellaneous, (4 folders); (1 folder) (Box II:546)
    - California
    - Capital punishment, (2 folders)
    - Central Intelligence Agency
    - China, (2 folders)
    - Christopher, Warren, (2 folders)
    - City Year (service corps), Boston, Mass., (2 folders) (Box II:547)
    - Clinton, Bill
      - General, (3 folders)
      - Staff
    - Clinton, Hillary Rodham, (2 folders)
    - Committee to Protect Journalists, (2 folders)
    - Congress (Box II:548)
    - Constitution
    - Courts
    - Crime, (4 folders)
    - "C" miscellaneous, (1 folder) (Box II:549)
    - Defense
      - General
      - Nuclear weapons, (2 folders)
    - Drugs
    - "D" miscellaneous, (2 folders)
    - Economy, (1 folder) (Box II:550)
    - Europe
    - "E" miscellaneous